Look at my box, baby. I get that you're going.
So they've been re-screening my outside all day with Android.
That upside. Nobody wants to hear about you.
Nobody wants to give you attention and you surely aren't getting any positive attention here.
Trust us
These guys come to my house for what the tree they want me to pay 10 grand to fucking cut these motherfuckers
You guys gonna hear it right now you're gonna hear it because the one on the back
They're trying to get me to pay not even on my property because it touches
I'm afraid to go on a show, yeah, I'm afraid.
I mean, they're in the chat.
Hey, Eliza, I'm so afraid to go on the show.
Why, because he has people just harass me
and then he makes money.
So I'm like, not gonna go on a show again.
I'll be in a stupid chat.
Have I ever considered getting a dog?
Well, I have enough cats.
Oh my God, they're so, I mean, all they have to say is,
he digs in his ass and he has shit in his nails.
I mean, it's like, that's like,
Either something that bothers me or something that's like going to try to like
Hi, something that's gonna like, you know make people just associate bad things because they keep saying I mean
It's like over and over and over. I mean they they're like, oh, let's just say this over and over again
to try to like destroy
his image
So this is like, okay, so first of all this is like, okay, I just want to remind you what these people these women look like
Have you ever seen witches of Eastwick? Well, you know, it's not Cher and Michelle Pfeiffer. I'll promise you that
Okay, it's like more like the Sanderson sisters, you know before they do the beauty spell
I mean, I'm not I'm not being mean. I'm not being mean or trying to be mean or just I'm not I'm not kidding
I mean, it's like this is honestly what they look like
I'll show you. I mean, it's like I'm not even like a friend. They're gonna just bully me everywhere
I'll show what they really look like because they look like their character. I mean, I'm not like an old 75 year old bitch
Name Christine. Nothing. There's anything wrong with being any age or whatever. It's like, please be proud of your age
Whatever, but she's gonna say I'm old
She's 30 years older than me
and good times looks 30 years older than me.
I mean, I don't understand what's going on here.
So let me see, where is this?
I have a picture of Christine.
Oh, yeah, here's Christine.
Okay, she says, I'm disgusting.
Here's her in the photo she was using.
What happened with her?
I don't know, but here's her catfish photo
and there's her real self.
I mean, Eliza Dushku or I mean what I think I think speaking of Howard Stern
I mean she Howard Stern's wife that looks like you know, Beth Etruske
About 30 years ago, maybe but she's really let herself go since I mean, it's a I mean and this is like what three months
Imagine imagine how much he's aged since then. I mean terrible terrible
And she's talking to me about my looks and my,
and bringing my family into it.
Like, you know, I'm allowed to talk about my family,
just like she's allowed to talk to her son
or put her son on the phone.
Just because I say something about it doesn't mean
it's meant to be for her to go to every show
and get all personal with like my,
and it's like, she doesn't even get the facts right.
I mean, it's just like all around like bad,
like kind of like, you know,
thing with everybody.
Yeah, and then here's Amanda.
I mean, you're like sponge, I mean, yeah.
If you're a fan of SpongeBob SquarePants,
you might think she's cute.
She looks like a piece of eatin' cheese.
I mean, and her tie needs to go over her sponge.
Yeah, that's Amanda.
So these women, when I like, you know, make fun of me.
Basically, they'd say I'm gonna send sisters.
Oh, man, oh, and it's money for 20.
It's not talking about things like,
oh, I'm gonna send you money for this and this,
and then you're not.
You're not so stop staying it
It's not funny when you do that. It's called a financial trolling
If you're gonna say I'm gonna send me $2 just send me the $2 don't keep saying I'm gonna do it
Oh, so you can buy shampoo so you can buy your nails. And what are they talking about? Oh, Christine's like, oh
Well, he hasn't he had asked for a donor to send a shampoo
Where did this come from?
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, it's like, I can show you the shape.
No, a donor didn't send me the shampoo.
Let me just show you what I have.
I mean, it's like, I have like stuff.
I like stuff in my shower.
Hold on, I'll show you what I have.
I mean, it's not the most expensive beauty products,
but here's what I have.
I mean, it's like, I have, your back,
I have like this, this is native body wash cucumber.
And man, it's not dollar stuff, right?
It's all the short stuff.
I have Pantene, Ned.
Netto Netto yaj
Okay, classic a big bottle of it. Okay. I mean I have a St. Ives
Apricot looks like Christine's husk right in there, right?
It looks good, right? And then I have a toothbrush and a toothpaste. I mean, it's like so I
Mean, it's like I mean I do my best. I mean, it's like I'm not like, you know the human body, you know, but the good thing about
And I'm not bald like I mean it's like oh and here I'm bald like I have like like for I mean
It's like for person with so much like hair
I had like so much air, like I'm so not balding at all.
But I mean, it's like, I'm certainly like accused
of like, you know, terrible, terrible things.
And money, it's like, you know, it's like,
I've been so supportive of you.
I had your channel up advertised for a long time.
I never did anything bad as a mod.
You have mods attack me like Bronzebird
and Christine say, get the fuck out.
Like it's her chat.
It's her chat until you mean to get the fuck out.
You said they're laughing about her dumb nail joke
that she's told like 20,000 times.
And it's like, not even like true, right?
Don't know. It's like are people retarded. I guess I mean, it's like yeah, I know money for 20 is kind of slow
And you think Sandman's bad?
Try reasoning with money for 20. I mean Jesus. I
Mean, I don't even know what what his race is or language. He speaks. I don't know. He speaks. He speaks dumb
He's like stone. I mean, he's not terrible person, but he's just like such a follower and
Not respecting other creators
Christine's not even like her.
I mean, Christine, I mean, it's like,
yeah, just start your show again.
I don't know, do some kind of like, you know,
the view or something.
Oh, you're not, you're not Joy Behar.
You just look like her ass.
Christine, I mean, you're not, you're not Joy Behar.
Who do you think you are, Christine, doing a show?
Who do you think you are?
Well, who do I think I am, right?
I mean, it's like, he's not Harrison.
You know, I'm not Harrison.
I wake up every day, I look at my bank account.
I'm like, I wish I was Harrison.
He has a billion dollars.
You know, I have like, it's their 10 cents, okay?
So I understand, I get that point.
But who is this, who is the celebrity on your show?
And, oh, and you have a celebrity, pay all attention,
I pay all the attention to me.
I did, okay, so I wrote a song for him.
I had him on for two hours talking about whatever he wanted.
I showed him a couple of things I've been working on
because I'm also an artist and so it's like sharing.
And I had nobody else on at the same time.
I mean, what else can I do?
To have a good show. I mean, it's like I
Made I take my interviews. I make you know documentaries out of them that people love
I mean, it's like so I mean what I mean is you have to criticize just to criticize at this point
I mean, it's like it only is it's like it's like it's so sad when it's like the person actually like respects you or like
You know think you're
Probably pretty pretty brilliant. She probably does, you know, it's like but she's but she has to say like lies
I mean they have to say things like oh, he's he's Syrax. He's bald. He's dumb
He's this cuz just people they just hope people will believe it. I mean are my nails perfect. Well, this one's not bad
But you know, are they perfect? Is that shit? No? I mean, it's like I don't know. What is it? It's like
tobacco and
You can see the tobacco on my table. I mean, so
But anyway, I'm not balding.
No, I'm not.
Oh, and then money for 20.
Oh, oh, I don't wanna see you in the Speedo.
Oh, really?
Then why are you playing clips of it on your show
and like laughing at the clip?
I don't know.
No, you would love to see my Speedo.
The thing is I'm not gonna waste my Speedo on your show.
to have someone kick me off. I mean, I'm not gonna waste it. It's like, the speedo needs to be respected.
I need to be kicked off the show fair and square, not like, you know, after my speedo comes off,
not off, but, you know, out. And Katrina, I took a bath last night in the speedo. I mean,
like people, these people are just so far behind, they just assume, oh, go take a bath. I'm clean.
I mean, it's like, I'm so clean, like, you know.
Guess what if they want to lick my asshole? I mean, it's like I mean how how clean do I need to be for these women?
I mean, I know I'm not even in the same state as them
They seem to be so cared about so keyed into my hygiene. Do we understand how bad Christine's vagina smells?
Do we do we even know do we do I keep saying oh Christine? I bet you have a smelly twat
I could say that like every show whenever she comes anywhere. I'll start saying that as long as you keep saying
I have dirty nails because it's like I don't even care about my dirty nails
My dirty nails are like, you know the sign of a good terror reader. That's what they say like in my vocal orange shit
But what's it? What's uh all dirty snatches is is is offensive to everybody? Okay?
Are these people that know know about tarot and care readers understand?
You know the dirty nails. I mean, you know life lived
I mean, how much shit do I have in my ass
between my nails so dirty every day?
I mean, it's like, I don't know.
I mean, it's like, I mean, I usually like, you know,
we'll use like, you know, toilet paper or something,
not just like, you know, wipe with my hand.
But if I think this is India.
But I mean, no, I mean it's like I don't know if that mean it's like I think that's what they're confused about
They're like, well, they're like, well, I wipe my ass
they are their ass with their hands and they don't get shit in their bigger nails because you know, they were there were those
You know those cheap, you know, lady Maybelline
Whatever those nails are called. I don't know press only press on nails
And so they just like peel them off and there goes this shit. I guess I don't know, right?
I just don't understand.
Why are you on, how many accounts are you on, Eliza?
Hi, oh, hey, IRL News Time, how are you?
I'm sorry, I was just like, you know,
I go over to Money 420 just to like, you know,
say hi to everybody instantly,
but she keeps saying every time,
which is just like trying to like smear me is like,
oh, you have been digging in your ass with your nails,
and that's why they're so dirty
and you need to take a shower.
I mean, they just say, but they say this every time.
Sure, sure, sure.
Yeah, I'm sorry. I've just I got kind of
They irritated then money for 20 is like
In the back and it's like and he's like oh, he's so too afraid to come on
Why cuz I made him a hundred dollars the other night from Christine kicking me off the show
He was you won't come up here. He knows like I yeah
I think I refuse to make money for 20 any more money from Christine just having me kicked off the show
But anyway, good morning everybody. Hello, like geez
I get triggered a little bit going to these shows.
I go try to be friendly and have fun,
and then there's people in there
who might want to be friendly and have fun.
And then instantly on the panel, Amanda, Christine,
you know, they have pictures of animals.
It looks like they're, you know,
those animals are good-looking animals.
I'm not gonna try to disparage them
by comparing them to their owners or whatever.
Anyway, hi Lenore, how are you?
I mean, oh yeah, I mean, it's like, oh, and you know,
and then if that doesn't work,
then they start bringing up the cats and all kinds of stuff.
Okay, good morning, or good afternoon.
Hey, we are in the afternoon.
Hello, how are you?
Hey, how are you doing?
I'm okay today. Yeah, I mean I had like a little I mean he saw last night
Minnie Manson was on the show and I had a good interview with him and yeah
I haven't I haven't watched the full episode because I was doing something but I will I will I it looked interesting
It looked really interesting. Um, let me I want to say I want to talk to you about I tried to call you privately
But um, your phone wouldn't let my number come through
I paid right that's why that's why okay um
I think I figured out why
Good times had an issue with you or might take an issue with you
Yeah, I'm banned
I know why um
Are are you and j-dog still friendly or not?
Well, I did I mean I taught him he had said oh, let's I'll take you out dancing to a gay club or something like that a couple weeks
To go and I never like you know reach out to him personally
And so we never did anything and I haven't really seen him since then. Well, he's doing a lot. Okay
I'm gonna actually do a recap about this because it bothers me
I was looking at some of the streams that Trip and Sip has archived over on the Rumble channel and Tommy did a stream recently.
J-Dog was on there, Goodtimes was on there, someone known as LB who I'm not familiar with was on there.
J-Dog proceeds to start talking about me. There was no reason for my name to even have been brought up.
No one else brought me up on that panel but him.
Then he proceeds to talk about Tommy needing to meet up with me to clap my cheeks.
which obviously Tommy was uncomfortable with.
He actually panned the camera away from him
to his notepad where he was drawing.
Because Tommy and I have a little bit
of an unspoken agreement to where we both stay
in our own lanes, which I'm very appreciative of
at this stage.
And then he proceeds to talk,
I mean, he was just really degrading to me.
Um
Good times didn't say anything directly, but he was obvious by it
That's why I'm gonna recap this because it was weird the other guy on there
I could tell had a little bit of an issue with what was being said
Then he continues, what else was he saying?
Oh, he was saying that I'm quote unquote special,
again, in a very disparaging sort of way,
and said that I'm one of those who never leaves their house,
even though I would say I've met more streamers
than most within these communities, okay?
So,
J-Dog, you know, as you know, I thought I'd made peace with J-Dog, but I think that people are
Aligning you two together and that could be why you're encountering some issues. I don't think it's you
I think that people are putting you two like as like a pair
And that's what the issue is okay, so I'm not I'm mad about it
Well, actually I am a bit angry about it because again, I thought that
There was nothing else for me to say about J-Dog because I thought that he had nothing else to say about me
But he's basically doing what Tommy used to do which is use me as a
Mechanism to hate bond or as a topic of conversation for no reason in order to network or make friends
Yeah, so
You know, and I just noticed who he's aligning himself with
Clumsy and Carl right and Eliza Eliza has a good point in chat
She goes j-dog wants in attention negative reaction
You know what I mean all he gets out of saying stuff is a reaction
I would say yeah, he I think he really just try to like fit in the places. I'm you know like you know
and seem cool like one of the guys wherever he goes he's like a chameleon in that way where and then it's like but then he'll
You know, I'm probably real god don't talk about women the way that he's been talking
Right, I know I know he's been it's his mr. Is this misdirected
Misunderstood way of like I guess trying to like bond with people and it's sad like I've never I never heard him
Like you know say anything like the only thing I talked to him
I talked to him on the show and stuff like that and you think you were in the chat and he was like
Oh, you know, like you know, let's let bygones be bygones and that's what that's all I'd seen
I thought we were done. I really thought he and I were you know done, but apparently not and
I don't like it. You know, I'm at a point in my life to where I'm not just, you know, quietly shouldering that sort of insult and whatnot anymore.
I'm just not. And if you hear this J-dog, flow your roll and cut the crap. Okay. I didn't like you from the start. I tried. And now you've done too much.
So if anyone out there is aware of him let him know exactly what I said that he's doing way too much
And he needs to keep my fucking name out his goddamn mouth at this point
It's not any boys club
Yeah, and those boys that you were talking to you better believe
They would rather deal with me than you any day any time you ain't shit
So that's it. I'm done. But yeah, that's what I wanted to let you know because I think
That people are linking you two together. I think that's a part of what it is
Well, I went on a get-times last night and I I speedo bombed him and I did that to a few places and
You know because it's like getting close to fourth of July. I'm just getting in the festive mood
And, you know, so, he said he's not bringing on the panel again.
And I was like, well, good times.
I didn't, I mean, it was just by Speedo.
And he's like, he's like, I'm straight.
And, yeah, I know he's straight.
And then in money for 20, he's like, oh, I don't want to see that.
I was like, I got my speedo in the chat.
He's like, no, I don't want to see that.
And then I found out he played it on his show.
Like somebody else played, I mean, it's like, it's like, they love it.
And then they pretend like they can't, they hate it and stuff like that.
But they love it.
I mean, people, everyone where I did it.
I did it, it got a funny, it was a funny reaction.
It's a lighthearted thing.
It's not supposed to be offensive or like,
but now it's like, oh, Christine's calling me sex pest.
Oh, I'm, you know, all this stuff and.
and says I didn't like oh and then my interview is bad because I think I'm Howard Stern and then
and then I didn't pay enough attention to Minnie Manson. I wrote Minnie Manson, I did Minnie Manson
a live song on the air um and then well he was on for a long time I mean I didn't see it I haven't
watched it yet and he seems like a really interesting person and someone who's you know
interesting entertainers like him, allow you to interview them, but...
That was because I went on the, you know, I made the...
I took my old episode where I interviewed him and I put it through like, you know, notebook
and then it had like a little mini-documentary with all the information that was presented in that episode
and it came out really, really well and so I guess Nancy,
about the episode, and so he contacted me.
He's like, I want to be on the show again,
and I love, thank you for making
such a beautiful, nice documentary.
And so I was, I'm just smoking tobacco here today, guys.
I'm maybe not a weed to the unfortunate,
my weed, my paper is done.
But yeah, but I had a good time of...
of last night with Minnie Manson, and it was fun.
And it's like, yeah, and it's like, yeah, sometimes I,
like, if there's like, not like a lull,
because there's no, everything's interesting with him,
but I did want to share some of my music with him
and get his opinion, because he's also like, you know,
a musician, and also I let him choose the genre
for the song I made for him last night.
And it's like, so I was able to personalize.
I did also this other thing
That also does a reading I went through that with him and personalized this whole thing and that's whole story came out
And it was like he got emotional. It was it was it was like really really good
It's like so I'm on the right track with like what I want to do with like some guests like that like
during interviews and stuff and so I feel like
I don't know, whatever people can criticize,
they'll criticize, you know?
But most of it is like not really fair,
I think towards me,
and I think they're just angry at me, like, you know,
for other reasons, because it's like,
they're saying things that are not even true,
and keep saying them over,
the same things over and over again,
trying to like hammer them people's minds,
these negative associations to make with me.
And that's like, I see it,
but I don't know if other people do, and so.
Well.
Yeah.
You know
It's like every single time the last ten times
I've been on a show with her where she has clapped me off several times
She says the first thing she says is oh, you're digging your ass with your nails
Wait, wait, who are we talking about here? This is this is Christine and then I'll then um
Well, you already know that Christine is going to be a certain way with you at this point, right?
Well, yeah, I know but it's like I mean she's like
Very vocal get the fuck out of here. She's sex pests like when I go in any chat. I mean, it's like I
Actually the female
Equivalent of what I'm contending with when it comes to J-Dog really think about that. It is it's the same thing
Right. There's they're saying nonsense in order to their same things in order to
You know, like you said, they're saying it repetitively to solidify it in people's minds
So what's the solution to that? Don't interact, right? That is and it's like a dog
He's a bully. Okay, and there's only one way to deal with the bully as you know
So I'm gonna be now. It's different in your situation because she's female in your male
So it's you know, it is different, but yeah
I don't like to are you seeking out Christine? So you guys won't wait did you go on her panel?
No, I was banned before I ever was allowed to even I can't even be in her chat or a panel like nothing
Like I was always banned from her show immediately like and so I'll have run into her at other places like Stephen King's money for
20s
Summers channel and things like that and then and then she'll be like get the fuck out of here if she's a mod
She'll usually like or she's allowed to so try to cloud me, but they had to tell her just to stop
kicking me out for no reason, which is like what she was doing, and Bronzeberg too.
And then I was like, well, just mod me here so they don't do that. And then it's like,
well, I can't have a lot of mods because that's a lot of problems. Well, I don't do anything as a
mod unless I'm asked really by the host to do it. And so it's like, I'm not a bad mod. Plus,
it's like, I mean, I do have some experience on streaming and stuff like that. So I just don't
know. I don't know if Christine blocks everyone's eyes, but I know I'm
I know Crystal Marie tends to block everyone in the chats,
but yeah, I don't know about Christine.
She doesn't, no, she doesn't block.
She always wants to interact, interact.
And then, oh, what else she'll do is she'll jump on the panel.
If I'm ever on the panel and start screaming over me,
she's like, I'm not gonna let you talk.
I'm just gonna talk,
and then she'll start screaming about the nails
and stuff like that for, until I leave.
And then they'll be like, oh, he raged quit.
You know, I just can't, I guess can't get a word
at edge-wise.
And so it's like, I just like, never mind.
But yeah, it's my fault for going to these places
that I shouldn't, you know, it's my fault.
I'm to the point to where I just don't go anywhere, but I feel this, you know, negative towards me, but at the same time
I'm not going to tolerate, you know,
unprompted, unjustified
talk of me like what J-Dog is doing, and you know, we do have to look at some energetic balances here because
What you condone and others often does come to you
Right, that's what I'm thinking when it comes to myself. So it's telling me I probably need to modify
And I believe that like
A bit right well
Yeah, sometimes it's our actions, but it's like we have but but I do believe what you just said like it's so true
Like I think like however we make people feel like we will feel like that someday too, especially
Right. Yeah, so it's like yeah, so that I just try to I mean I don't want to I don't go away
I'm gonna tackle you know, it doesn't look good with like me like attacking women
But it's like like, you know a woman or whatever Christine, but it's like, you know, if you see how like, you know
Unprovoked and nasty and like person and then she keeps bringing my family my family
Oh, your sister your mom is paying for this your sister's doing this and this I mean it's like and I'm like well
She's not don't talk about family on any point in time. Did you two ever get along?
Christina and I were friends for months. I mean for a long time. She was a white cause the ripped
Well, because Crystal Marie came on one day and was like Christine kills kids and I was like I was like no
I was like not the Christine we know and then she's like yes
She doesn't she's in a gang and she is she has you know these 80 year old men and rascals
You know it has her enforcers and stuff like that. I just I was Crystal Marie be Crystal Marie
You know, I was like, you know Crystal Marie's
Sometimes ridiculous like that and so I kind of I didn't play along with her
I was like but then and then Christine kept saying oh
I just let her say this and this and so I played the thing a few more times to show that I was like saying no
This is not like I but then then the Chrissy's like well you keep playing you keep playing it
And so hey scum however something about what crystal Marie said though that really hurt her feelings, right?
We'll see but you ever apologize. Yes, I did I did
Specifically about that incident. Yes, and we made up actually we made up for like over three days
and unfortunately like and then have been a few days later. I was on and
I made a joke because I guess clumsy bean gang was like,
hey, he's like, do you ever think there's a curse on you?
And I'm like, yeah, I was crying into the ether.
I saw Christine around a tree with a bunch of like women,
like they were sacrificing kids.
I remember that.
Yeah, and that's why-
Yeah, okay, okay, that's, okay.
Here's where you're really pissing her off, okay?
And I don't talk to Christine just so that you know,
and I'm sure you know anyway,
because you and I talk all the time, but,
She's a mom isn't she I think so I think she's a grandmother. Yeah
Say that kind of stuff when it comes to her it obviously hurts her and you are poking her
I've apologized for both of those things, but it's like well you apologize
But then you did it again, and you do have a habit of doing that at times
I'm not you know chastising you, but I'm just telling you that
You do do that you repeat even though you know it's wrong
Right. So that's probably what her issue is and if she's a mom does she have sons?
Yes, but she was telling me that's considered so she's looking at you as though you should
Know better, but you're not thinking about her feelings
You're not, and I don't mean to be mean, but I'm listening, and I'm trying to get to the
bottom of what it really is, and that's what it is.
The stuff that I said about, like at that time, that was around the spider ritual time
when she was involved with that, and also like when her saying, oh, I need to go jump
off a bridge.
And then she said, oh, well, no, she was like, well, she was fighting back.
Well, I was fine. I mean, it was like that was like that was like before any of like the other like the second time whatever happened
It's like we went through phases. It's been going on for months, but it's like another one of those things where it's like a lot of it
Yeah, when I'm with Bita too, she's like so like she's like, Oh, Bita doesn't drink.
Bita's perfect.
Like Bita's, Bita is like the best person, you know, and it is her friend.
Yeah.
But it's, but it's very obvious.
Like, it's like, okay, so if you're a friend, then you're going to like every love everything
and everything is great.
And if you're like, if you're like, sometimes it's like that, as you know, yeah, yeah.
I know.
I'm giving you a hard time, but you're, you're, you're, um.
I know I'm not perfect
At times I can I can be a little picky and choosy also. I can also be hypocritical at times. Okay, right?
But you know what I would do if I were you what's up? I would do a
specific solid
Authentic only if you want to because maybe you don't want to but a specific authentic sincere
one stream, keep it under five minutes, genuine apology to her.
And then I would just never ever talk about her
or the incidents again.
Yeah.
That's what I would say if I were in your position.
She's watching the show.
She says, oh, you know, the worst show, whatever.
She's always, she knows everything about it,
everything that happens.
I mean, she's like, she's watching.
But does that tell you?
You know, it tells you that she's looking for
you to, well, basically do what I just suggested, but you haven't done it yet, and it also shows a level of her caring about your opinion, whether she admits it or not, and I think it's something about, like,
The only things I really know about her is that she does something in the medical field
and that she's a mom and a grandma. She also seems to be a very sensitive woman
who is very, you know, who really guards her friends. That's my impression of her.
So, if there was talk of, you know, children being harmed or something, that would definitely
bother the kind of person that she is extensively, and that's probably why she's taken issue.
And you know, different people have different tolerance levels for different things.
And we have to, you know, acknowledge that and whatnot.
She would probably be very cool with you if you were willing and maybe you don't feel like it
It's okay if you don't but I I know I have to modify
Myself when it comes to certain people that are in my life. I have to tone things down sometimes I have to amp it up
but with her you just have to tone it down in order to
communicate with her because I think that
through the aggression or the
assertiveness that we see
Maybe there's something about what was said that really triggers her and it could be more painful than you or I could ever imagine
Right and I and I will back. I mean I would I backed off that I mean it's like I I don't I didn't keep repeating it
It was said one time and then she keeps but you did repeat it
right you did and then
Whenever she hears or sees you it instantly makes her think about that because she didn't get closure
the situation. Yeah. She needs the closure. Yeah. So, if you, you know, I guess, and I
hate that the word coexist. I've always hated that word, okay? I'm trying to, you
know, help you out here. If you want to be able to go on these panels where she's
obviously a consistent figure, you're gonna have to learn to coexist with her,
you know figuring out a way to genuinely not only just apologize but stick to the
new boundaries that maybe she has because she is she is a little bit older
than we are yeah and you know again we don't always know
What a person has gone through but when somebody has such an it's you know an intense
Reaction and she has a very intense reaction to you from what you're explaining
Something bad happened. Okay, and that's what
Has to be acknowledged even if we don't know and she never needs to say what it is
But I just get this gut feeling that something happened and that's what I don't think you're understanding
Because you're taking it as a personal attack and I don't think it is
I think if anything you're a sort of an avatar or icon or representative in her mind to whatever that incident
Or situation may have been that bothers her so much
That's very wise, you know, and you know, I mean I will back up and I have backed off
It's like, you know, I don't go in there saying
Get the fuck out Christine or like, you know, just bringing stuff up
I'm I don't even talk to her but she but she's attacking like a rabbit pit bull at this point and it's like
Wow, I can't do anything. I mean when I first met her she said oh, you know, she's like my name is not really Christine
I named myself after that car in the Stephen King book, which is I mean, it's a killer car. I mean, it's like
And so it's like, and so for her to say, oh, I was doxing her.
She said, oh, well, what if there's like, you know, some accident and someone gets hit by a car
and then their parents go and they see that she's like the nurse and then they
the kid dies because they won't let her treat them or something.
I mean, it was just like this very farfetched.
Well, you see, there's a reason as to why, you know, and this was who?
Crystal Murray. This was Christine. Oh, Christine, Christine. OK.
I don't know her. I mean, that's the thing. I don't know her, but as I've told you there's always been something about her that I really like
And I just think that she may have seen and dealt with more in her life than she cares to tell us.
And it's not her business, but what I do know is that oftentimes people who are in the medical field, whether it's a paramedic or a nurse or, you know, whatever, a doctor, anything, even an ambulance driver, they often...
the worst of the worst, frequently.
And when they leave those professions, it's hard.
It's almost like a veteran going to war
and then having to, like everything's okay
when they get back to their home country
and everything seems okay, but they can't forget.
So that's what I think it is when it comes to her.
And I think that if you were to do
video just for her and really mean it and then stick to your guns and forget
about all the you know back and forth with her and just go about fresh I'll
bet you she would end up being cool with you again because she does strike me as
that kind of person but she just doesn't want to remember something
Okay. Yeah, I understand. Yeah, I can see that probably. I mean, it's like, I need to be like,
sometimes I tend to like, sometimes step on people's triggers without trying because it's like,
my mind is like everywhere, like a lot of places. And so I say like a lot of different things.
And it's like something will probably like, you know, connect with, and they'll probably say,
oh, this old trucker probably, I don't know, I just tend to do that sometimes without trying.
And so it's not malicious or something like that. And
And I'm on a show like, you know, it is kind of like,
I'm not like a different person or something like that,
but it is like-
Well, you're a lot of different people.
Let's keep it up.
But I am too, and it's okay.
But, you know, you're figuring out
what primary person you wanna be right now.
And I know that.
I just wanna do, I mean, it's like, I mean-
It's like it's hard enough like without all this all the criticism even for like it's hard enough with it
You know, there's criticism that is valid
But it's like when there's all this like invalid criticism that's being taken seriously by other people
It's like that's just kind of annoying
But and it's like not just her it's like a lot of people are throwing these storylines about
Animal abuse or or you know, I hate my or my cats hate me or you know, I'm just like this
evil, filthy, dirty person.
And I'm just like, I'm so bad.
And it's like, sometimes even the AI will say,
you know, I'm some kind of like, you know,
manipulative mastermind character and stuff like that.
Which is like, it's like, it's like,
so it's like, there's like some,
there's like views that are like,
maybe the things like look like certain ways
on the surface and the people aren't picking up,
this was already in new windows,
like the little, like the little,
like the little minutia about stuff like,
that is like being misworse.
Like I am,
Not being serious like a lot of the time like sometimes I am joking and trying to get a laugh
Or sometimes trying to be outrageous a little bit. I don't know. I mean, it's like there's different things
It's like, you know, it's like I kind of like get out of body sometimes when I do my show, you know
And how long have you and I known each other now? Has it been a year? I think it's been close to a year, right?
It's been close to you. I think it was like probably like
Just maybe August or September or something maybe even earlier like I think it's been about a year though
Yeah, but I need to like a look look the first. Yeah, I'm gonna look right now because I'm not sure how long but
When I first when I first came across you and don't get Matt when I say this, but I'm keeping it real today, okay?
You had the exact same complaints
But you have grown since then your show has grown your online presence has grown your acceptance level has grown
the things that
You're upset that people are saying about you you could take some actions
to
Fix it, but you haven't and it's been a year. Do you want me to give you a list as to what you could do or no?
It's time for you to change your setup as far as your camera and your seating arrangement.
Uh-huh.
I want you to make the camera eye level or slightly pointing down.
I want to be able to see either a desk or a table in front of you.
and I want you to put that green screen behind you
and I want you to start using the green screen properly.
I want you to make it look a little bit more professional.
Your goal from what you've told me
since I've known you has been,
I want my show to be a real thing.
I want to be respected.
I want to be the Howard Stern kind of
entertainer. Well, if you want to do all that, then you need to step it up a little bit. It's been a year. Okay. It's been about a year. I'm looking right now to see, because I'm curious as to how long it's been that I have known you at this point.
I know September was the first time I think we started September. We did some streams
But it has happened
I'm just gonna say I've known you a year. So yeah, okay
Let's see. I'll say no well August August 24th. I think was the first well. That's when I did the psyches friends
Okay, so it must have been August cuz I because I think I was in Joshua tree at the time and that would have been August
So we're approaching that time again
Yeah, it's time for you to
You you could
prevent or stop some of these attacks by simply and I'm not saying you have to
change I mean you could just tell me fuck you bitch go to hell don't tell me
what to do you you could say that to me but what I've learned in life is that
When things, you know that are because these are all little things, right?
But if it's bothering you that much if it's bothering you that people are saying, oh, he doesn't care
He's just doing this. He's you know you present yourself differently because I think
Internally you are very professional, but I want your internal self to match your external
I've seen you, you know, get into modes to where I feel like you're starting to, you know, pull it together and, you know, really like, you know, pull yourself together and present yourself the way that I know you should be presenting yourself.
I'm not saying you have to be straight or conservative or anything like that, but you can, I just know you.
Being being as much as you can be online when it comes to your online work
amazing
But I want the in-person
Which is your camera you?
To match the codex
Okay, it's time. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna start
shifting into
The production value on the show. Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of things I can do that will help that and
It's all easy all I want you to do change that. Do you have a tripod? Do you need a tripod?
I have
Well the cameras on like the unlike legs, you know, but it's just like it's like not they're not very tall
And so it's like I need to like put them on something to make it like, you know more eye level
I have I want yeah, I need to be eye level now
or slightly pointing down.
I want it to look,
cause you'll also end up getting more readings
because I know that people who routinely get readings
like it when the person that they're getting the readings
from has like a certain kind of like look to their thing.
You can do that.
Cause I mean, you have the talent.
Why are you holding yourself back?
You know, when I was doing the,
I'm not even gonna call them recaps. I'm gonna call them mean caps when it came to Zaya pebs and duchy
I was specifically saying when it came to Zaya
He self sabotages. Okay, cuz I see how he does it
You're doing it a little bit, too. Now. I don't care about Zaya, but I do care about you. I
Want you not to self sabotage
That's me and Alex for today. That's me me. I had to but you just can't I want to see
Just you don't have to step it up a lot, but just a little bit just a tiny bit
Yeah, I hear that. Yeah step in my game and
Make it the show I want it to be I mean it's like I'm in the transition and Troy period right now
Which is always like they're kind of like you know a little bit volatile sometimes, but it's like I think it's going the right direction
I think it's like, you know
But I need to, yeah, I'm gonna do the production value up
and have more of a, sometimes topics of the shows,
have more of an organized show, have more of a gift.
Well, I mean, the start of it, I mean,
look, you've had a good year, okay?
But the many Manson thing, I mean,
I'm just skimming through the VOD right now
as we're talking.
That's that's the kind of guest you need a lot of I like this. I like that because he's kind of like, you know, the whole
Very dramatic and whatnot. That's you that that's that's your niche
but in order to attract that and I get that there's a level of
What's the word I want?
Nostalgia, maybe that maybe that's not even the right word, but to how you have your setup right now
but I just firmly believe that if you were to
just
Make it more of a desktop. Maybe not even desktop because I know I think you do have a table in front of you, right?
Is that a table? Yeah, it's a copy table. Yeah, okay. Yeah
You're joking to where we can see I think it's gonna look better if it's eye level
We can see a bit of what's on the table
You could do like the card readings to our like you know the readers put the cards on the table
Yeah, you could do that and and people want to see that
Is there anything that we that it is there a reason that you don't want to show the table?
Well, the table tends to get like, you know, I've covered tobacco and like a little bit like messy and like a little bit
but I know I need to
Basically, just go through clean really well have it or get it organized to get a system go and get an ashtray
Get it, you know, yeah, maybe like, you know smoke a little bit less out of the out of the bong dig a little bit less through the stuff
Yeah, well I'm being hard on you today. You're absolutely fine. It's like I know I need I need some tough love and you know some real talk
You know a lot of times I don't want to be like that's what it is
I think you know because you get upset and I'm not talking about this moment
But when these things happen with these people online when they don't let you in the panel you get upset
You you go into a certain mode you come back over on your channel over here
you you you know often sometimes you you cover your head with your little blanket
and you go go to sleep and you get see I don't want to see anymore of that the rest of the year
no more you're a big boy now okay and um I know you I know aside from all this you've been going
through a lot truthfully I completely know but I'm here to snap you out of it thank you okay
Because I've known you for a year and we're not going into a whole another year of you and I knowing each other
With these same complaints when these complaints can be
obliterate it by just shifting a teeny tiny bit and you're not even shifting you're just
bringing within from what's within you more so into the external the material world because
you're already at way ahead of your competition look at everything you've built for yourself online
it's beautiful okay but you've got to make what people see of you match that
And once you do that, they can't say anything anymore.
Right, very wise.
And yeah, I'm going to really take that to heart.
And.
So I do see like, you know, I do see like, there's like definitely the possibility of
even like great success I can have through this, you know, and it's like, I've done some
of the right things.
I've done like a lot of the wrong things I've learned a lot, you know, you have to go through
some of these situations and learn, make the mistakes and step on the landmines and survive.
And I'm still hanging in there as long as, you know, as far as I can see, I'm still
Good people to talk to and like not having everybody just being so against you
It's like it's they really does help to have you know a bright light like a friend like you and some other people that have been
They're really
Give me good advice and the motivation and a desire to improve and
Do better for everybody so and then maybe that will help other people do better too
I don't know it's like, you know, but you put out good things in the world and then like it can have good ripple effects and stuff like that
And so yeah, thank you. Well, you're just about there you really are you're just about there, but
I'm telling you it's gonna make a world of difference. Just change that camera angle put that green screen behind your
couch and
Well, yeah, it's like it has to go on to my uh, I'll need like a ladder
If there's a stairway behind me, so it's like that so that back wall that's what's that's that's what's behind that
Yeah, there's a stair the staircase is there, but that's perfect. That's per I that's better
Yeah
Yeah, do you have any um
I'll need it next time. There's a handyman or something. I'll see if you can nail this up there like on the other side
No, you just need some tax let like pushpins or take a lot. Yeah
Yeah, and I'll just take like a ladder though because it's like up to stairways. It's like
You can you can there is there a ladder in the maintenance room of your complex there probably is my garage
Let's take my garage. There might be one in there
I mean, uh, so yeah, I'll look into that all right people in the chat
They are co-signing on the green screen repositioning project
2023 5 1 1 is whoever that is
Yeah, it's 20. Yeah, and you might want to turn it when you do reposition it turn it
90 degrees you want it to be
Horizontal yes
you home and I'm gonna play the piano so do you need a tripod you know I'm
willing to invest in your show I will send you a tripod there's like there's
like see this is like how big it is I'm picking up the camera right now but
there's like this tripod that's something the tripods and maybe yeah that's
that's that's too small you need a real tripod
And the camera like you know tricks was like got into like very now how now how what what kind of that camera you have is it a
Phone camera, or is it a webcam? What is that that you're that you're shooting camera? I got it on team. It was a 4k
HD on the bottom of it. Does it have like a
Thing to screw is it like a little thing that a tripod could screw into or does it need this a tripod need to have like a clamp
I'll see if I can all I'm gonna unscrew the tripod and show you right now here
Here's this here. This is a tripod that screws into it. You can see how it goes. Okay, so there
There's a tripod
Oh, so it has a little okay, I see your okay, and that's how big it is
It's like it's like pretty small, but uh, and then that screws into the top right here
It's not I mean, it's not an expensive camera. It was a pretty good deal. You know, it was like, you know
Yeah, but so but you need a tall stable
Yeah, okay, that's best I can do right now. All right. Well, I'm gonna get you a tripod
Hopefully it can yeah, you know, I'm I'm here for the show
but
Find that ladder today or tomorrow and re reposition that green screen and that way we can um
You know amp you up a level. That's what we're doing
And we only got NorCal in the chat. I haven't seen NorCal in here. I don't want to talk to that one. No, he's not coming up
He's just in the chat. He's good. I mean, I did I see yeah
He's just give me how I was died Doxton, but he's actually appeared on my show shirtless with his gray chest hair
Yeah, he's been showing himself lately. Yeah
Yeah, so I didn't dox you you're already on my show on camera, sir
And I didn't use any of your real names. All I know is your name is NorCal
So well, I know what his first name is and one day I'll know his last name and that will be the killing strike and he knows it
I better get going I gotta get going. I'm gonna do a stream this afternoon because I gotta
There's a few people that I need to beat down and
But all right, so look for that ladder at some point today and I'm going to stay on your ass about that.
and at least consider the Christine video.
I will, I will, thank you so much.
It'll just make your life easier
and that way you can visit your friends on their panels, okay?
And you're not just doing it for yourself,
but you're doing it
because she does need some clear, I think, okay?
Thank you, thank you so much.
I love you even though it's me and to you today.
It's okay, you're good, you're good.
Thank you so much for the great advice.
All right.
Wonderful day, I'll see you this afternoon.
Okay.
Okay, come on.
Bye-bye.
Okay, bye.
NorCal, you did say I was a doc,
so you said it and you commented on one of my music videos
during the live and you said, you called me,
you said your doc seemed pop off.
Okay, let's see.
Oh yeah, we have a couple of guests here.
Oh, look at how beautiful he is.
God damn, is that fucking sick? Yeah
Dude, you gotta fucking get some braces nigga Jesus, bro
God damn. It's like a fucking dude. Hold on a second. Do you know that fucking that game of Candy Crush?
Yeah, fucking you know that little fucking creatures and they're like, you know doing all that movement
That's exactly this motherfucker looks like oh my god. Hey psych. I never said shit about you doctor
I have to do a surgery wire my jaw shot for six months. Oh, no. Yeah, you need your jaw wired for six months
Oh my god
That's as big as a penis extension and your jaw wired. I agree. No
cap papa
No one said shit about you Docs and me bro. I don't give a fuck
But I wasn't that but I wasn't trying to mean I was
You're just trying to fucking, you know, you're just trying to rule the foot
You're just trying to rile the hornet's nest
Hey, bro, hey check it out, you know, I'll fucking put it turn the camera right now
I guarantee you I'm a lot older than you, but I look younger in you. That's the sad thing, bro
I have less facial
Black guy's bathroom.
You've got some fucking facial words you need to remove
before they turn dangerous.
Yeah, no facial words.
Yes, you do.
What the fuck is that on your cheek?
That's a titillation.
That's a fucking cancerous.
He's got AIDS.
Oh, shut up.
Psyche, he didn't take your prep, bro.
Come on.
I don't, I'm not on prep.
I don't have AIDS.
Psyche, you don't take, are you serious?
You don't take prep?
I'm not on, I don't have AIDS.
I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with people, I don't even have sex with
They have vacuums NorCal. Yeah, no, no, you don't own one. You've never turned around.
Some people don't. Show vacuum.
These guys are lame. You guys don't have sex.
Show the vacuum, bro. Show vacuum.
And I'll show my fucking Spyderco vacuum.
I have more sex than both of these guys combined.
There's my vacuum. See it?
Hold on. I'm going to show you my vacuum.
I'm gonna show you my vacuum, bro. Hold on. I'm looking for I'm looking looking looking
I've got a shark like six teeth, baby shark to do to do to do to do
I never want to blow jog from sick if you would bite off my weenie. Well, no
I mean you got to have you got to have tack and you got to have fucking you got to have
I don't want to say anywhere when you're my dick, you know, I think this report reek and people Harry tatsy kiss
His name is the guy's name is
Money or what it's it's a food stamps and
A guy named LES. Now I'm in love with all of these Puerto Rican guys.
Yeah, you couldn't handle a, you couldn't handle a, you couldn't handle a Vato, Papa.
I have-
You can barely even handle a fucking white boy.
i'ma realign your jaw i've been with mexican gang members i've been with several actually
i have you my type and unfortunately because it's like you know hey look i got something to
show you hold on sir i mean i've never been with somebody like this that's willing to willing to
willing to do uh do you know anything about pebs and zea's pistol play and all their sexual
They play with guns.
The line is
not going to do anything for this.
Whipping all the things, sir.
If this line isn't going to fix this.
No, no, no, you're going to need fucking hardcore braces.
Like I'm talking about, you know,
braces are not going to fix this either.
They need to break my jaw.
What did you do?
Say, how do you what happened?
They need to break my jaw.
They literally need to break your draw.
And then they wire your shit together.
It's crazy how did why is your job broken in the first place?
This is literally it was a crazy ass injury when I was maybe like six or seven years old
involved. NorCal, you can't have firearms on your channel. You realize it, right?
Yeah, but you just can't. You can't point it at the screen.
But just so it doesn't...
You can't have any firearms on YouTube.
Yes, you can. They're gun channel sticks, so what are you saying? Just make some sense.
I'm just telling you, I'm just trying to fucking throw you a bone here, buddy.
Well, throw me a boner. I'm horny.
Fucking retarded homosexual.
Get out of here. Out!
I want to talk to NorCal alone. Okay.
Well, I'm not, Norka, can you come pick me up?
I'll get in the car with you any day.
Look at your shoes.
Look at those shoes are filthy.
I thought I had dirty shoes.
Hey, look at, you wanna see something crazy?
My Birkenstock, which is my dad's Birkenstock,
it has a hole in it now.
I wore a hole through the Birkenstock.
Have you ever seen anything like this?
And that's crazy.
There you go.
I don't think he knows he's on camera anymore.
Norka, you're still on the air.
Oh, there goes that.
Well.
That was exciting. That was exciting. Okay, let me get my
Let me get let's go to it. No, do you know that's what I walk to get cigars with me?
You see I just need to log into my phone and then we can go for a walk
And then I might have to take care of some business. Oh, I'm getting some messages
Okay, my message failed to send. Okay. Okay. No, unfortunately, I'm out of
data today, so
Yeah, he's a plumber
But anyway, okay, so Christine, let me just do the apology Christine
I'll apologize for those inappropriate jokes. Oh
Here he is. He's back. Hey, hey, thanks for let me look. I fucking I fucking left the fucking streamer
It's good looking out for let me know that uh, it doesn't end when you say it does yeah
Because I pushed the fucking you know the pink arrow to the right over there on the bottom of the ledger
I was like, your car, I was like, be careful Norka.
I mean, I was like, can I get a ride?
Did I dox myself?
Did you see my license plate?
Or do you know my license plate?
I just saw your shoes.
I saw your shoes.
You saw my rubber boots?
Don't do what I used to pick up dog shit in my backyard.
What do you think?
You want to try some rubber boots, papa?
I thought those sneakers.
They ain't sneakers, bro. These ain't sneakers in your car though. You're passing. Oh my truck. Yeah
These ain't shoes, bro. These are work boots. These are what people work in
Oh my gosh, these are work boots and these are bottles that I've gotten collected digging in people's yards
These are antiques and stuff. Look at that old fucking, uh, makeup, um, which you call it
It's an old ass bottle. Look at that. It's old bottles, bro. You know, they cool
an old Dick's vapor rub.
What do you think about it?
I'm through like the washing machine
and like, you know, repurpose them and stuff.
You know, people collect these in the dirty south
and people collect them.
Look at this old fucking bottle.
You keep them dirty or you wash them?
Well, I'm, dude, I'll give them to a friend
that actually has a fucking massive collection of these.
What's like the oldest bottle that you found?
Because I know someone said it found an old, full bottle.
The 1700s, well, I found some, dude,
we've dug under the Pepsi plant here
To my truck getting fucking dirty, dude. I got a vacuum this bitch. Yeah
No, dude, dude check it out. I saw you over at Jansons shit
Look, I was lurking over there
But uh, you know what try to reinvent yourself and let me let me just give you a pro tip do it with people that ain't aligned with
Fucking with teenage people teenage kids teenage girls. Do you saw the proof dude?
Don't fucking try to fucking downplay it. Just like
Well, yeah, I mean it's not I'm talking about some guy trying to encourage a fucking teenage girl said she was in fucking eighth
There's ninth grade or whatever talking about go ahead and drink drink drink drink all that that wasn't
That wasn't a troll. That ain't troll moves, bro.
That's inappropriate. That girl did have like...
No, it's beyond inappropriate, dude. It's despicable. It's what...
You know what I was doing out in my backyard?
That's what needs to be done to those type of people.
Okay. Well, I mean, right. Okay. Well, yeah, you see, you see, you see the thing is, you
don't, you don't know what innocence is because you've never been around it. You don't have
children. You don't, I mean, you're, you're kittens, but they're innocent. Okay. Your
kittens are innocent.
Yeah.
But, um, I saw that one attack you. It was the black one, by the way.
He's an outdoor cat. He's been
You should know better you should use the cat guy ain't you ain't you the terrible cat guy. You should have known better to fuck with an outdoor cat
You're lucky. You're lucky you didn't get a feline aide from that cat, bro
Good times is a fucking creep dude. He's an actual fucking creep
So if you're gonna listen to any no no that guy's confirmed a creep if you do what he does in video games to fucking
You don't think it's real life. You're a creep period
Dude, there's no line to be drawn between what is good and what isn't.
What is evil and what isn't, right?
You know what evil is, don't you?
You know what evil is.
Evil is what he did to those sins.
I wouldn't say you're evil.
I wouldn't.
You're not good.
You're not cool enough to be evil.
No, I am.
No offense.
I am so much cooler than you thought.
Well, what are you?
What is this picture?
Are you a Goetia demon?
Like, you know, that black guy?
No, I'm a fucking, I'm nothing.
I'm a fucking plumber.
What's up?
You got any pipes in here?
I have a very avatar with that, with that Machiavelli.
That's not what that is.
That is Pepe the Frog as anonymous, with an anonymous mask.
You don't even know what the fuck you're even talking about.
Oh, anonymous.
Okay, that's Pepe the Frog with an anonymous mask, right?
Yes, that's exactly what it is.
100%.
Has been since day one.
Okay, okay, maybe not Machiavelli.
It's nothing fancy.
So, I mean, look, have you ever been bitten by a horse fly?
Like a big fucker. I'm talking about a big giant black one that'll overwhelm you and scare the shit out of you when it lands on
He's been bitten by a horse, but not a horse fly
Have you heard of the power exchange in San Francisco, California?
The power was but still have horses or horse flies. No, no, I asked you a question. Have you heard of the power exchange?
That were used Pierce
I don't know but I've never pierced there, but I've seen people that I've told jury to and made custom jewelry for there
What does that matter? What does that matter?
No, I like that about you. I think it's creative
I think it's just part of the gay history that you're part of
I'll do it. I was a huge part of it. No. Now was I the main gay guy or the straight guy that used to make the jewelry for him?
I wasn't fuck here moose afar. I wasn't him. I wasn't fucking Jim Ward
I wasn't those people, but I worked for them and I made custom pieces for them. Yes, I did I
Worked my way up. I worked my way up as a fucking 18-year-old kid
Polished in fucking bullshit jewelry in the back of somebody's fucking bullshit shop in Southern, California all the way to the main custom jeweler
Took over the fucking owner bested him and anything he could do in that shop and took over his role
And I and I fucking was fucking his sister and had a fucking kid with her. What do you think?
Yes, they know know a thousand percent fucking gay guys are the coolest fucking things to the sliced bread
They're very peculiar very clean very neat and very smart and they have the best drugs of anybody in the world
Right, and they never get busted and they never get busted
Well, because well, I'm just telling you from what my experience. I mean, you might have more experience where you get your dope
How about we link up off this and you send me an eight ball of meth, what are you thinking? I got cat bro
Let's talk app. Let's talk off the air. All right. All right. I don't want any white. I want it. I wanted I
Want like nanobot Andy. I want clear. I want clear
I don't have drone. I don't I really I'm like I'm like a gay guy
Come on bro. Come on bro. Dude. Come on. Actually you're talking about a fucking actual fucking x method
You're gonna fucking tell me you've never
He dabbled in the fucking the crystal art
I've talked about bro. Don't fucking don't listen be
Listen, you're your best your best chance now is to be honest and just own what the fuck ever
I did it for you. I did it when I was a teenager. I did it for you. You did it. You did it a couple of days ago
Stop it. Stop it. Come on, bro. You fucking lost fucking 40 pounds in fucking two weeks. I didn't lose 40 pounds
Something like that
No one cares who's ugly and who is oh, he's talking about a cigarette me broke is it look
I've never claimed to be some fucking, you know poster child for the fucking
We talking about yeah, you didn't see it never mind what would you show let me see would you show to see it again?
You see your fucking cocks even gotten smaller dude. You're fucking dude. You used to have a pretty decent bulge now
The bitch is fucking shriveled up like your arms and legs
Canceled you're done. So bro. You're done. So if Kate the turtles listening. What's up, Kate? You're done, bud
You're done. You're canceled your fucking cock is shriveled. You used to have a pretty decent sized hog now
You're fucked. I can't get much
Your bull just junk
That doesn't matter no one wants that fucking let me see you let me see what show the fucking the cotton crotch in those
No, we'll talk real size
What's a real size your fucking skinny legs and arms? No, sir. That's nothing the men don't want that
I'm they just don't or women
That's too skinny, papa.
Does it remind you of the American flag?
No, it reminds me of somebody that had the bad one
that was in the hospital getting fucking injections.
That's what it reminds me of, no offense.
Good lord.
Damn, well shit, what's up?
What's up, NorCal? You didn't like it?
Well, the date's off.
When dude, you've already said I'm a hideous old man. You would have nothing
Just basically you said that
I don't even want that I don't come on the internet for relevance or any type of fucking kudos dude
I'm not here for that. I'm here for the lol. So I want to be laugh now me shooting that gun in my backyard on your stream
That made me laugh
Well, I mean having the camera on after me freshly cutting the grass and you know not going around the fucking swing set or whatever
Going across the fucking crusty as drill. I'm gonna give a fuck dude. I'm not trying to hide who I am
I don't give a shit
I don't want to be doxed obviously because I'm not fucking human, but I mean because I have shit to lose
That's why I don't cam up. Dude. That's not because dude. I'd have a show
I'd have a fucking litty show if if I wanted to
But I have to lose dude
If you got in a Speedo and were laying in your backyard like Tricia Licious, I would watch you.
I mean, it's like, I mean, can you do that?
Dude, Tricia Licious, what do you want to watch that fucking shriveled up Creech for?
I don't know how I want to watch you.
You're the founder of the Bad Moms Club, which is the current high-coin.
I know, I'm not the coin eater.
So you get Alex Mayer's, you get Alex Mayer's in here talking about how Bad Moms Club,
this and that bitch, I fucking hashtag coin that bitch since fucking 2017, 18.
You're leeching and creaching off me, Alex.
You know, me and Alex, me and Alex went round and round with Nuka Zeus.
Matter of fact, me and a couple of my partners were the reason why she drove to Florida and met
that motherfucker. Never let her forget that, that a fucking chat always wins and I'm a chat troll.
I'm a junky one, but look, at least I did a couple things that were
some funny, a little bit funny. Her meeting up with Nuka Zeus, that was funnier than motherfucker, dude.
That was funnier than a motherfucker, and she knows I'm responsible for it.
It was good content.
Me and my friends, you know, I had a couple of friends,
you know, we conglomerated behind the scenes.
That's what, you know, that's what actual fucking...
The shit should be made for, but you know, people use it for other things, video games, and whatever.
I tried to meet Q. I tried to meet Q. I tried to meet J-Dog. It seems like they just want to rate, like, uh, like a rock.
What are you going to meet these guys for, dude? You think they're gonna, well, Q45 might actually fuck you, because he's a faggot, but I digress.
I know, that's why I want to meet you, I'm gonna go dance.
Yeah, no, it's possible, it's possible.
Let me tell you what you're gonna have to do.
Q45 is a little peculiar.
He might be a fucking fag,
but he's gonna need you to clean your fingernails.
Real good, I'm talking about-
I will, I will.
They're a wife.
I'm talking about pulling up to Bita's house,
fucking trolling Bita, standing out,
knocking on her car windows, knocking on her door,
and getting you to take you to get a fucking manny petty,
nigga, pay attention.
Yeah, go to beat us now get fucking take you did I'll give you a hundred bucks right now to fucking go to be the front door
I'm not being serious, dude. I'm not being serious. I don't want you to go because be
To you be that will kick the shit out of you physically
That's not that's not that's different. That's you know, you're talking about witches and warlocks. So, you know
We're talking about castles and whatnot
Let me see what you're doing, what are you trying to do? What are you doing? Go ahead?
I do do do your best impression of me, bro. Go ahead. I'm happy dude. I love it
Save that fucking beard dude you look like a creature
I think the one that listen, you know, nobody cares, but um, I would never
He showed me his penis
No, no, he he's famous for that imagine show is that you call that a penis? I call that a fucking
I call that a fucking skin tag. It bet it looks like one of those Indian burial. Oh my god
It looks like a skin tag that I got on my fucking nipple
It looks like some my pulled off my chest before just just because it looks like a tick. It looks like the fucking tick
I know. It's like a hairy thing.
Who did Ziggy eat?
Look, man, you know, if I didn't have shit to lose, I'd turn the camera on, lift my shirt up.
I'd show you my bulge, Papa.
I'd show you my bulge, and I bet my bulge is bigger than yours.
And I'm a little bit bigger than you.
As far as weight goes weight category
Can we compare sometime NorCal? I think
Look it's possible if you you know if you fucking
refute the demons that you've had in your possession
These demons
Repent my nigga
I don't have a for dude. I'll fucking 20-20 fuck off bag it. Oh, I'm sorry maggot
fake it, whatever, anything but the actual word.
You know, listen, I love the fucking...
I don't know if I love it. I was a big fan of the LGBT community when I when I was working there because I was shown
Nothing but respect and given the best dope. I've ever had my fucking life right this was 30 years ago mind you
But still dude, I'm gonna tell you what every time dude when I worked in San Francisco
I did service plumbing every time and if I you know, you'd have to call the people right you get in the truck
You call them right?
Hey, yeah, this is, you know, if I heard any kind of, like,
gay accent, yeah, sure, I got, I ain't gonna say I got excited,
but I was looking forward to see what was on the table.
Thousands of times, hundreds of times I went in there.
Oh, you know, help yourself.
And there was a table.
It was like going into a Mexican pharmacy
with all the good shit right on the counter.
Have you ever been to Mexico?
Yes, yes, several times. Yes.
Have you ever been to a drugstore in Mexico?
You were in a pharmacy, and you just say, oh, Bizanax?
No, no, no, you have to speak Spanish with the terms,
otherwise they're going to bring a kid out.
Oh, Viagra, Viagra?
Oh, no, you need to know all of the things, anyway,
but I'd be going with the Mexican.
No, that didn't you know, you know, then they'd tell you to get and then you wouldn't they wouldn't give you shit
You get the bunk shit you but I'm gonna tell you what they do stills make they make
They make what hold on a second not meet you a condo make. Um, what are those fucking things called in scarface that I smoke?
No, hold on a minute. Hold on. I'll think of it. Give me a second. I'm getting old
Shit, what the fuck were they fucking called anyhow
I'm 25% Mexican. Are you Jen? Are you? Are you? Why is that? Why is that? Because you're husband?
Where's your husband?
Is he an amigo?
You see I don't even know anything about him. He looks as white as he looks like your brother. No offense girl
Norco, what if I did steroids that would help me if I gain like some some
I think laying off the methamphetamines would help you gain weight, but no
I mean more eating than taking stolen coffee from Asians and fucking eating french fries. Yes. That's what I think
Okay, first of all, I'm so sorry. Oh the surgery you've had in Mexico. I got you. I got you
I didn't steal anything. Well, you're trying to chew down at the fucking Asians, which isn't gonna happen
Are you new to the world? You don't do Asians. You don't do agency. Dude. That's the last thing you do is try to
I mean maybe a quarter I mean, but dude you're trying to rip them off a dollar
They'll come out hard like they did on you pay attention
I paid with a debit card, it was a new chick at the front desk, she's like the granddaughter
or something.
And I heard with you, dude, listen, I pay attention, I'm pretty smart.
Look, what about a dollar off?
You tried to like say, you know, for a dollar, because that's all you had on your card or
whatever.
And then you fucking ran out and got wrecked.
It's all like, fuck up, I made a fool of myself on the internet.
It happens, bro.
I've done it plenty of times.
Well, I've made a fool of myself plenty of times on the internet, bro.
It happens.
It's, it's, it's, it's all right.
It's all right.
Okay.
First of all, that's only store, like nearby.
So I wouldn't do that to like the only store, but here, so let's watch to clip together.
Here's me.
They, they, I try to play, I try to pay for it with the credit card, right?
And she said, Oh, it went through and I, I've been in 17 years, Jim, but back in the
day, all you had to know was just a little bit and you get the good shit, dude.
I mean, you could get anything.
You get fucking liquid.
Liquid fucking methadone. You could get liquid. I'm sorry liquid morphine. You get liquid liquid anything
Anything liquid you could get the problem was was getting them
See the thing is you had to drive in you couldn't just walk in and come out with the shit because
The second day if they'd catch you with that you'd get wrecked
I sketched i'm fucking having a couple italian-made switch planes down my fucking boots one time, you know
I mean I made it through
But then you get a little braver and you, you know, a couple of bottles down your boots.
They're not going to check you because you've obviously been partying.
You go in with a, you follow with a group of people.
If you stand out, you stand out.
If you get fucked, you get fucked.
That's the way it is.
But go ahead.
This is a three minute clip of the incident.
But do you see on the screen question is advised.
What you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna do, what you gonna
I asked her, I asked her.
Oh yeah, I said, I said to her.
I mean, they ran out like I'm robbing the store.
I told her, I said, I said, I think I,
can you do a dollar on each?
No, I'm kidding.
It's okay.
Yeah.
You're going to call the cops.
You're going to call the cops?
Okay.
Well, come on.
What are you?
I don't know.
I called you.
I wanted to call you at the screen.
I asked her.
Yeah.
Did I ask you?
I asked her, lady.
Hey, ma'am.
I asked her.
Okay?
I know.
I asked her.
All right.
Thank you.
Go, you fucking boys.
Please.
Please do raise your voice.
You raised your voice at me.
Yes, I'm raising my voice.
She told me that it was okay.
No, she did.
Yes, she did.
You're going to play it back?
Wow.
What are you raising the voice for?
You're raising the voice of me, Ron.
You're raising the voice of me.
Okay, you're on camera.
Okay.
Everyone sees how you act.
You try to get away from the feeling.
Oh, really?
Wow.
I tried to steal.
That's all, folks.
I asked her, did it go through.
I didn't say, can I have like a dollar off myself?
Did it go through?
Yeah, I did.
she's like oh it's fine and that's what i asked her about okay anyway good god right okay say
i can't take anymore i need to go give some i need to go to that very store right now and get to
mcdonald's but i can't take i can't take uh with me unfortunately but i'll be back later this afternoon
and what should we play what should we play this here's a mini manson song i made last night for
That was just fine
Got a question mark, catch
That's the game, place my video